fastsigns.com 2008-12-16

# Digital Sign Solutions, Graphic Services, Signs, Signage: FASTSIGNS®

**FASTSIGNS INTERNATIONAL, INC.** **_Privacy Policy_**

At FASTSIGNS International, Inc., ("FII," "we," "us" or "our") your privacy is of paramount concern to us, which is why we have developed this Privacy Policy (the "Policy") to explain our practices regarding the use and disclosure of information we may obtain from users of our FASTSIGNS Site, located at www.fastsigns.com and related sites (collectively, the "FASTSIGNS Sites"). We believe that our practices allow us to provide great offers to you, without unnecessary use or disclosure of your information. This policy is incorporated into, and subject to, our Website Terms of Use Agreement (the "Agreement") . If you have questions regarding this Policy, please write to us at or:

|   | FASTSIGNS International, Inc.,  
Attention: Webmaster - "FASTSIGNS International, Inc. Privacy Policy"  
2542 Highlander Way  
Carrollton, Texas 75006.  
---|---  
  
**_Site Operation And Production_**

The FASTSIGNS Sites are operated by FII and exist for the purpose of disseminating information about our company and our FASTSIGNS® services and products, and to provide a mechanism for users to order our FASTSIGNS® services and products online through our FASTSIGNS Centers, which are owned and operated by independent third party franchisees or other parties.

This FASTSIGNS Site is controlled, and all information that you submit through this FASTSIGNS Site is collected, stored, and processed in the United States.

**_Adult Use_**

This Website is intended for adult use only, and we do not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18 or not deemed an adult under the law of the jurisdiction from which the individual is accessing this FASTSIGNS Site.

**_Collecting Information_**

We generally do not collect any personally identifiable information from individuals unless specifically provided by the individuals. For example, you voluntarily provide your name, postal address, email address and phone number to us when you register with a FASTSIGNS Center, purchase products or services from FASTSIGNS Sites, provide feedback on our products, or apply for a job online. We generally use this information to improve our FASTSIGNS Sites, respond to your requests and provide the good or services you order. We also collect information in the following ways:

  * **Franchisee Applications:** We permit users who are interested in franchise opportunities with FASTSIGNS® to submit franchisee applications online through FASTSIGNS Sites, [franchise.fastsigns.com](http://franchise.fastsigns.com/). If you choose to submit a franchisee application through the FASTSIGNS Site, we will ask you to provide detailed and verifiable information, including your name, your spouse’s name, your contact information, your Social Security Number, and information about your work and professional experience, your educational background and personal and/or business finances. In addition, we will ask for permission to conduct a check regarding your credit history, work experience, criminal records, and general character. If you do not consent, we will not be able to process your application. We utilize industry-standard SSL technology to allow for the encryption of all franchisee applications submitted on a FASTSIGNS Site. For additional details about our information security practices please see the section entitled **SECURITY**. If you are still uncomfortable with submitting a franchisee application via the Internet for any reason, please feel free to print a copy of the [franchisee application](https://franchise.fastsigns.com/franchiseeApplication.html) and submit a completed application via facsimile ([click here for our fax number](http://franchise.fastsigns.com/franchise-request.html)) or by mail ([click here for our address](http://franchise.fastsigns.com/franchise-request.html)). 
  * **Electronic Mail:** We may retain the content of any e-mail that we receive, the e-mail address from which it is sent, and our response. Content and other information in or related to e-mails sent by you to us may be used as testimonials or for other marketing purposes in accordance with the Agreement. Please be aware that when you receive a receipt acknowledging your e-mail or your submission of an order or application form, it means that the message or form has been routed into the Internet, and not that it has been received by us. 
  * **Promotions and Sweepstakes:** From time to time, we may offer promotions or sweepstakes on our FASTSIGNS Sites. When you enter a promotion or sweepstakes, we will require the submission of your name, e-mail address and postal address. We will use this personally identifiable information for purposes of administering the promotion or sweepstakes in accordance with its rules. Please note, sometimes the name, likeness, and other information is posted about contest winners in accordance with the official promotion or sweepstakes rules (but we do not publish your e-mail or street address information) on the FASTSIGNS Sites and you hereby grant us permission to do so. 

We may share any of the information we gather on our FASTSIGNS Sites or otherwise maintain with our affiliates, franchisees, and service providers (for more information please see the section entitled "Sharing Your Information" below). We may also collect and store statistics and other information about the online activities of our visitors on an aggregate basis. For reasons such as improving your experience at our FASTSIGNS Sites or personalizing our FASTSIGNS Sites to you (for example, providing better product recommendations or special offers that we think will interest you), we may supplement the information that you provide with information from third parties.

**_Sharing Your Information_**

In the course of carrying out our operations and seeking to improve the content of the our FASTSIGNS Sites, we may transfer your personally identifiable information and other information that you submit on our FASTSIGNS Sites to our offices, affiliates, FASTSIGNS Center franchisees, and service providers in the United States and throughout the world. However, we will, and will ask our franchisees and service providers to, use, store and otherwise process your information collected through any FASTSIGNS Site in accordance with this Policy regardless of where it is transferred. We do not sell your personally identifiable information to third parties, without your consent, except to the extent required by law, in accordance with your instructions, or as set out below:

  * **Transaction Requirements:** FII and FASTSIGNS Centers sometimes retain the services of third parties to perform functions or services on our or their behalf. For example,we use service providers to send e-mails on our behalf; and our FASTSIGNS Centers create and deliver the FASTSIGNS® products or services that you order through a FASTSIGNS Site. To our knowledge, these companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. However, we do not undertake to confirm, investigate, or police their practices. 
  * **FASTSIGNS Centers:** We may send your information to FASTSIGNS Centers to provide you information or services that you request or that we believe may be of interest to you. For example, if you contact us regarding FASTSIGNS® services or products, we will ask one of the FASTSIGNS Centers which create and deliver FASTSIGNS® products or services, and provide quotes for such products and services, to respond to you directly or to provide you the quotes, products or services that you have requested. To our knowledge, FASTSIGNS Centers do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. However, we do not undertake to confirm, investigate, or police their practices. 
  * **Our Affiliates:** From time to time, we may send your information to our affiliated companies if for example, we believe that they may have information about franchising or other opportunities that may be of interest to you. 
  * **Joint Promotions:** From time to time, we may join with third parties to provide specific services or products. When users sign up for these services or order these products, we will share only the names and other information that is necessary for the third parties to provide these services or products. These third parties are not permitted to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services or products. However, we do not undertake to confirm, investigate, or police their practices. 
  * **Business Transfers:** As we continue to develop our business, FII or the FASTSIGNS CENTERS might sell or buy assets. In such transactions, user information generally is one of the transferred business assets. In the event that all or substantially all of our or any FASTSIGNS Center’s assets are acquired, user information may be one of the transferred assets. 
  * **Protection of Site and Others:** FII, our affiliates and each FASTSIGNS Center preserve and have the right to disclose any information about you or your use of any FASTSIGNS Site without your prior permission if we or they have a good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (i) protect and defend FII’s, our affiliates’, or the FASTSIGNS Centers’ rights, property or safety or that of other users of any FASTSIGNS Sites or the public; (ii) enforce the Agreement and Additional Terms or (iii) respond to claims that any content violates the rights of third-parties. FII, our affiliates, and the FASTSIGNS Centers also may disclose information as we or they deem necessary to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request. 

We may disclose aggregated information to third parties. This type of information is not linked to any personally identifiable information that can identify any individual person.

**_Contacting You_**

If you provide us your e-mail address, mailing address or phone number or other contact information, occasionally we or our FASTSIGNS Centers may send you email communications or call you from time to time to provide information or offers that we think you will find useful or of interest to you. You can choose not to receive any future promotional or marketing emails or other communications from us, FASTSIGNS Centers, our affiliates or other parties with who we share information by following the procedure described in the " **Controlling or Changing Your Information** " section below. Please note that we may occasionally contact you for administrative purposes even if you unsubscribe from our email or other promotional list.

**_Controlling or Changing Your Information_**

You may request to stop receiving marketing or promotional communications by sending us a written request to the address listed below or by following the opt-out instructions in the e-mail you receive from us. You may review, change, or request the deletion of your contact information and preferences at any time by:

  | E-mailing us at:  | webmaster@fastsigns.com, or  
---|---|---  
  | Writing to us at:  | FASTSIGNS International, Inc.,  
Attention: Webmaster - "FASTSIGNS International, Inc.  
Privacy Policy"  
2542 Highlander Way  
Carrollton, Texas 75006  
  
However, to the extent that corrected or deleted information is also stored in other databases, we cannot always ensure that such corrections or deletions will immediately reach the other databases. Some information may be retained for longer periods as required by law, contracts or auditing requirements.

**_Cookies and Web Beacons_**

We use cookies to assign a unique identification to your computer. Cookies are files that your browser places on your computer's hard drive, which we may use to learn how you arrived at our site. Cookies are also used to save and retrieve your e-mail address, password and preferences so you do not have to re-enter this information each time you visit our site. Cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our FASTSIGNS Sites. Users can set their browsers or third party software to reject cookies. If you reject the cookie, you may be unable to use portions of our FASTSIGNS Sites that require registration, some pages of the FASTSIGNS Sites might not function properly, and the FASTSIGNS Site experience will not be capable of being tailored to you from visit to visit. Please consult your web browser's Help documentation for more information about how to turn cookies on and off for your browser. Cookies are placed on your computer, and accordingly we neither store cookies on our computers nor forward them to any external parties

In some cases we may track or collect information about your use of our site by the numeric address assigned to the computer you are using (your IP address) or by the URLs that you come from or leave to. These methods also allow us to resolve server problems or administer our site. We do not associate this information with any other personally identifiable information that you may have provided us.

Certain pages of FASTSIGNS Sites and promotional e-mail messages or newsletters we send may contain electronic images known as Web beacons - sometimes called single-pixel gifs - that allow us to count users who have visited those pages and to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon. Some of these Web beacons may be placed by third party service providers to help determine the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns or e-mail communications. These Web beacons may be used by these service providers to place a persistent cookie on your computer. Doing this allows the service provider to recognize your computer each time you visit certain pages or e-mails and compile anonymous information in relation to those page views. These third parties are not permitted to use Web beacons to collect or access your personal information. However, we do not undertake to confirm, investigate, or police their practices.

**_Third-Party Web Beacons_**

 We use third-party web beacons from Yahoo! to help analyze where visitors go and what they do while visiting our website. Yahoo! may also use anonymous information about your visits to this and other websites in order to improve its products and services and provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by Yahoo!, [**click here**](https://ondemand.indextools.com/optout,OptOut.vm?domain=stats.indextools.com)

**_Security_**

We take reasonable precautions to protect your information. When our registration/order form asks you for sensitive information (such as credit card numbers and/or social security numbers), that information is encrypted and protected with industry-standard encryption software - Secure Sockets Layer™ (SSL) technology. If we do so, we will notify you at that time if such encryption is available. If you are still uncomfortable with submitting your credit card or other order information via the Internet for any reason, please feel free to print a copy of an order form and submit the completed form to a FASTSIGNS Center via facsimile or call in your order (click here to find the FASTSIGNS Center nearest you).

However, no security system is impenetrable. You understand and agree that data and communications, including e-mail and other electronic communications, may be accessed by unauthorized third parties when communicated over the Internet. You agree that it is your responsibility, and not ours, to protect the confidentiality of all access codes, passwords and user names, and to obtain and use third party software products that support encryption and other security protocols compatible with such protocols (if any) that may be used by us from time to time in connection with the FASTSIGNS Sites. Accordingly, we cannot guaranty the safety or security of your information and your use of the FASTSIGNS Sites and submission of information to us is at your own risk.

**_Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites and FASTSIGNS CENTERS_**

Certain FASTSIGNS Sites may contain links to other FASTSIGNS Sites or other third party web sites whose information practices may be different than ours. You should consult these other web sites’ privacy notices, as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties, unless otherwise expressly provided by us.

**_Limits on Our Abilities_**

Your privacy is very important to us. However, due to the existing legal and technical environment, we cannot ensure that your personally identifiable information will not be disclosed to third parties in ways not described in this policy. For example, we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. Additionally, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to private entities, law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to address or resolve inquiries or problems (our practices are more fully described in the section entitled "Sharing Your Information" above).

In any event, we cannot and do not guarantee that independently owned and operated FASTSIGNS Centers will follow the terms of this privacy policy. Therefore, if you provide information to any of our FASTSIGNS Centers, such information will not be subject to the terms of this policy.

**_Changes to Our Privacy Policy_**

This Privacy Policy became effective on October 9, 2008. We reserve the right to modify or amend this Policy at any time with or without notice, and for any reason. If we make material changes to our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on our main FASTSIGNS Site, www.fastsigns.com so you will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. You are responsible for reviewing this Policy each time you use or access the Website. Your continued use of this Website is an acknowledgment and consent to any terms contained in this Policy, as it may be amended from time to time.

©2005. **FASTSIGNS INTERNATIONAL, INC.** All rights reserved.
